<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Simple Caméra</string>
    <string name="app_launcher_name">Caméra</string>
    <string name="camera_unavailable">Caméra indisponible</string>
    <string name="camera_open_error">Une erreur est survenue lors de l\'accès à la caméra</string>
    <string name="video_creating_error">Une erreur est survenue lors de la création du fichier vidéo</string>
    <string name="video_mode_error">Échec lors du passage vers le mode vidéo</string>
    <string name="save_error_internal_storage">Une erreur est survenue, le dossier de sauvegarde a été changé vers la mémoire interne</string>
    <string name="camera_switch_error">La permutation de caméra a échouée</string>
    <string name="click_to_resume_preview">Cliquez sur l\'image pour reprendre l\'aperçu</string>
    <string name="photo_not_saved">La photo ne peut pas être sauvegardée</string>
    <string name="setting_resolution_failed">La définition de la résolution a échoué</string>
    <string name="video_recording_failed">L\'enregistrement vidéo a échoué, essayez d\'utiliser une résolution différente.</string>

    <!-- Other aspect ratio -->
    <string name="other">autre</string>

    <!-- FAQ -->
    <string name="faq_1_title">Quelle valeur devrais-je mettre pour la qualité des photos ?</string>
    <string name="faq_1_text">Tout dépend de ce que vous voulez en faire. Pour la plupart des usages, il est recommandé entre 75 et 80%, ce qui est reste de qualité acceptable, tout en générant un fichier de taille bien inférieure à une photo avec une qualité de 100%.</string>

    <!-- Settings -->
    <string name="save_photos">Sauvegarder les photos et vidéos vers</string>
    <string name="show_preview">Apercevoir la photo après la prise</string>
    <string name="shutter_sound">Son de l\'obturateur</string>
    <string name="back_camera">Résolutions de la caméra arrière</string>
    <string name="front_camera">Résolutions de la caméra avant</string>
    <string name="photo">Photo</string>
    <string name="video">Vidéo</string>
    <string name="focus_before_capture">Mise au point avant la prise</string>
    <string name="volume_buttons_as_shutter">Utiliser les boutons de volume comme déclencheur</string>
    <string name="turn_flash_off_at_startup">Désactiver le flash au démarrage</string>
    <string name="flip_front_camera_photos_horizontally">Inverser horizontalement les images de la caméra avant</string>
    <string name="keep_settings_visible">Garder visible les boutons de réglage</string>
    <string name="always_open_back_camera">Toujours ouvrir l\'application avec la caméra arrière</string>
    <string name="save_photo_metadata">Sauvegarder les méta-données exif de la photo</string>
    <string name="photo_compression_quality">Qualité des photos</string>
    <string name="shutter">Obturateur</string>

    <!-- Strings displayed only on Google Playstore. Optional, but good to have -->
    <!-- App title has to have less than 50 characters. If you cannot squeeze it, just remove a part of it -->
    <string name="app_title">Simple Camera - Capture photos &amp; videos easily</string>
    <!-- Short description has to have less than 80 chars -->
    <string name="app_short_description">Creating memories has never been easier. Provides a nice interface with no ads.</string>
    <string name="app_long_description">
        This handy camera is usable for both easy photo taking and video recording. You can quickly switch between the front and rear camera, modify the save path or limit the resolution. You will never miss the important moments of your life. There are many helpful settings available to make it even more personal, suited for your needs. Let\'s list some of them.

        The flash can be turned on and off or used as a useful flashlight, which is not seen often. You can pinch the screen to zoom in and out or toggle horizontal image swapping during capturing fantastic portrait photos.

        You can easily change the output resolution, quality, or aspect ratio with a few clicks, as you would expect from a modern camera app. This applies to both photos and videos.

        After taking a picture you will see the new photo thumbnail, by pressing which you can quickly open it in your preferred gallery. You will see a clear indication of when the photo gets captured, guaranteeing that the file has been saved.

        If you want to launch this easy camera at pressing your devices\' hardware camera button, you might have to disable the built in Camera app in Settings -> Apps -> Camera -> Disable.

        In case you prefer quality over speed, you can enable an option for always focusing the camera in before taking a picture, to make sure the result is crystal clear.

        You can configure it to use volume buttons as a shutter, or to turn on flashlight by default at startup.

        It has multiple other settings related to the shutter sound, flash, photo metadata, photo quality etc. The output file path can be customized, so you can decide where you want your media saved. It supports both the internal storage and SD cards.

        It comes with material design and dark theme by default, provides great user experience for easy usage. The lack of internet access gives you more privacy, security and stability than other apps.

        L\'application ne contient ni publicités ni autorisations inutiles. Elle est totalement OpenSource et possède aussi un thème sombre.

        <b>Check out the full suite of Simple Tools here:</b>
        https://www.simplemobiletools.com

        <b>Facebook:</b>
        https://www.facebook.com/simplemobiletools

        <b>Reddit:</b>
        https://www.reddit.com/r/SimpleMobileTools
    </string>

    <!--
        Haven't found some strings? There's more at
        https://github.com/SimpleMobileTools/Simple-Commons/tree/master/commons/src/main/res
    -->
</resources>
