<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Simple Camera</string>
    <string name="app_launcher_name">Simple Camera</string>
    <string name="camera_unavailable">Cámara no disponible</string>
    <string name="camera_open_error">Ha ocurrido un error al acceder a la cámara</string>
    <string name="video_creating_error">Ha ocurrido un error creando el archivo de vídeo</string>
    <string name="video_mode_error">Ha fallado el cambio a modo de vídeo</string>
    <string name="save_error_internal_storage">Ha ocurrido un error, se ha cambiado la carpeta de destino al almacenamiento interno</string>
    <string name="camera_switch_error">Ha fallado el cambio de cámara</string>
    <string name="click_to_resume_preview">Haga clic en la imagen para reanudar la vista previa</string>
    <string name="photo_not_saved">No se pudo guardar la imagen</string>
    <string name="setting_resolution_failed">Falló la configuración de la resolución apropiada</string>
    <string name="video_recording_failed">Grabación de video fallida, intenta usar una diferente resolución</string>

    <!-- Other aspect ratio -->
    <string name="other">otro</string>

    <!-- FAQ -->
    <string name="faq_1_title">¿Qué calidad de compresión de foto debería establecer?</string>
    <string name="faq_1_text">Depende de tu objetivo. Para propósitos generales, la mayoría de las personas aconsejan usar 75%-80%, y la imagen seguirá siendo de calidad realmente buena, pero el tamaño del archivo es reducido drásticamente comparado con el 100%.</string>

    <!-- Settings -->
    <string name="save_photos">Guardar fotografías y vídeos en</string>
    <string name="show_preview">Mostrar una vista previa de la foto después de capturar</string>
    <string name="shutter_sound">Sonido del obturador</string>
    <string name="back_camera">Resolución de la cámara trasera</string>
    <string name="front_camera">Resolución de la cámara frontal</string>
    <string name="photo">Foto</string>
    <string name="video">Video</string>
    <string name="focus_before_capture">Enfocar antes de la captura</string>
    <string name="volume_buttons_as_shutter">Utilizar los botones de volumen como obturador</string>
    <string name="turn_flash_off_at_startup">Apagar flash al iniciar</string>
    <string name="flip_front_camera_photos_horizontally">Girar horizontalmente fotos con cámara frontal</string>
    <string name="keep_settings_visible">Mantener los botones de configuración visibles</string>
    <string name="always_open_back_camera">Siempre abrir la aplicación en la cámara trasera</string>
    <string name="save_photo_metadata">Guardar metadatos exif de las fotos</string>
    <string name="photo_compression_quality">Calidad de compresión de foto</string>
    <string name="shutter">Obturador</string>

    <!-- Strings displayed only on Google Playstore. Optional, but good to have -->
    <!-- App title has to have less than 50 characters. If you cannot squeeze it, just remove a part of it -->
    <string name="app_title">Simple Camera - Capture photos &amp; videos easily</string>
    <!-- Short description has to have less than 80 chars -->
    <string name="app_short_description">Creating memories has never been easier. Provides a nice interface with no ads.</string>
    <string name="app_long_description">
        This handy camera is usable for both easy photo taking and video recording. You can quickly switch between the front and rear camera, modify the save path or limit the resolution. You will never miss the important moments of your life. There are many helpful settings available to make it even more personal, suited for your needs. Let\'s list some of them.

        The flash can be turned on and off or used as a useful flashlight, which is not seen often. You can pinch the screen to zoom in and out or toggle horizontal image swapping during capturing fantastic portrait photos.

        You can easily change the output resolution, quality, or aspect ratio with a few clicks, as you would expect from a modern camera app. This applies to both photos and videos.

        After taking a picture you will see the new photo thumbnail, by pressing which you can quickly open it in your preferred gallery. You will see a clear indication of when the photo gets captured, guaranteeing that the file has been saved.

        If you want to launch this easy camera at pressing your devices\' hardware camera button, you might have to disable the built in Camera app in Settings -> Apps -> Camera -> Disable.

        In case you prefer quality over speed, you can enable an option for always focusing the camera in before taking a picture, to make sure the result is crystal clear.

        You can configure it to use volume buttons as a shutter, or to turn on flashlight by default at startup.

        It has multiple other settings related to the shutter sound, flash, photo metadata, photo quality etc. The output file path can be customized, so you can decide where you want your media saved. It supports both the internal storage and SD cards.

        It comes with material design and dark theme by default, provides great user experience for easy usage. The lack of internet access gives you more privacy, security and stability than other apps.

        No contiene publicidad ni permisos innecesarios. Es totalmente libre, proporciona colores personalizables.

        <b>Check out the full suite of Simple Tools here:</b>
        https://www.simplemobiletools.com

        <b>Facebook:</b>
        https://www.facebook.com/simplemobiletools

        <b>Reddit:</b>
        https://www.reddit.com/r/SimpleMobileTools
    </string>

    <!--
        Haven't found some strings? There's more at
        https://github.com/SimpleMobileTools/Simple-Commons/tree/master/commons/src/main/res
    -->
</resources>
