<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Simple Camera</string>
    <string name="app_launcher_name">Kamera</string>
    <string name="camera_unavailable">Kamera ei ole käytettävissä</string>
    <string name="camera_open_error">Kameraa ei saatu käyttöön</string>
    <string name="video_creating_error">Videotiedostoa ei voitu luoda</string>
    <string name="video_mode_error">Videotilaan vaihtaminen epäonnistui</string>
    <string name="save_error_internal_storage">Tapahtui virhe, tallennuskansio muutettiin sisäiseksi tallennustilaksi</string>
    <string name="camera_switch_error">Kameran vaihtaminen epäonnistui</string>
    <string name="click_to_resume_preview">Napsauta kuvaa jatkaaksesi esikatselua</string>
    <string name="photo_not_saved">Valokuvaa ei voitu tallentaa</string>
    <string name="setting_resolution_failed">Oikean resoluution asettaminen epäonnistui</string>
    <string name="video_recording_failed">Videon tallennus epäonnistui. Yritä käyttää toista resoluutiota</string>
    <string name="camera_in_use_error">Camera is in use by another app, please close the app and try again</string>
    <string name="camera_configure_error">An error occurred while configuring the camera</string>
    <string name="camera_disabled_by_admin_error">Camera is disabled by the admin</string>
    <string name="camera_dnd_error">"Do Not Disturb" mode is enabled. Please disable and try again</string>
    <string name="photo_capture_failed">Photo capture failed</string>
    <string name="video_capture_insufficient_storage_error">Video recording failed due to insufficient storage</string>
    <!-- FAQ -->
    <string name="faq_1_title">Mitä valokuvan pakkauslaatua minun pitäisi käyttää?</string>
    <string name="faq_1_text">Se riippuu tarkoituksestasi. Yleisissä tarkoituksissa useimmat ihmiset suosittelevat käyttämään 75-80%, kun kuva on edelleen todella hyvälaatuinen, mutta tiedoston koko pienenee huomattavasti verrattuna 100%:iin.</string>
    <!-- Settings -->
    <string name="save_photos">Kuvien ja videoiden tallennuspaikka</string>
    <string name="show_preview">Näytä kuvan esikatselu kuvan ottamisen jälkeen</string>
    <string name="shutter_sound">Suljinääni</string>
    <string name="back_camera">Takakameran resoluutiot</string>
    <string name="front_camera">Etukameran resoluutiot</string>
    <string name="photo">Valokuva</string>
    <string name="video">Video</string>
    <string name="focus_before_capture">Tarkenna ennen kuvan ottamista</string>
    <string name="volume_buttons_as_shutter">Käytä äänenvoimakkuuspainikkeita laukaisimina</string>
    <string name="turn_flash_off_at_startup">Sammuta salama käynnistyksen yhteydessä</string>
    <string name="flip_front_camera_photos_horizontally">Käännä etukameran valokuvat vaakasuunnassa</string>
    <string name="keep_settings_visible">Pidä asetuspainikkeet näkyvissä</string>
    <string name="always_open_back_camera">Avaa sovellus aina takakamera aktiivisena</string>
    <string name="save_photo_metadata">Tallenna valokuvien Exif-metatiedot</string>
    <string name="photo_compression_quality">Valokuvien pakkauslaatu</string>
    <string name="shutter">Suljin</string>
    <!-- Strings displayed only on Google Playstore. Optional, but good to have -->
    <!-- App title has to have less than 50 characters. If you cannot squeeze it, just remove a part of it -->
    <string name="app_title">Simple Camera - Ota kuvia ja videoita helposti</string>
    <!-- Short description has to have less than 80 chars -->
    <string name="app_short_description">Muistojen luominen ei ole koskaan ollut helpompaa. Ei mainoksia, kiva ulkoasu.</string>
    <string name="app_long_description">
        This handy camera is usable for both easy photo taking and video recording. You can quickly switch between the front and rear camera, modify the save path or limit the resolution. You will never miss the important moments of your life. There are many helpful settings available to make it even more personal, suited for your needs. Let\'s list some of them.

        The flash can be turned on and off or used as a useful flashlight, which is not seen often. You can pinch the screen to zoom in and out or toggle horizontal image swapping during capturing fantastic portrait photos.

        You can easily change the output resolution, quality, or aspect ratio with a few clicks, as you would expect from a modern camera app. This applies to both photos and videos.

        After taking a picture you will see the new photo thumbnail, by pressing which you can quickly open it in your preferred gallery. You will see a clear indication of when the photo gets captured, guaranteeing that the file has been saved.

        If you want to launch this easy camera at pressing your devices\' hardware camera button, you might have to disable the built in Camera app in Settings -&gt; Apps -&gt; Camera -&gt; Disable.

        In case you prefer quality over speed, you can enable an option for always focusing the camera in before taking a picture, to make sure the result is crystal clear.

        You can configure it to use volume buttons as a shutter, or to turn on flashlight by default at startup.

        It has multiple other settings related to the shutter sound, flash, photo metadata, photo quality etc. The output file path can be customized, so you can decide where you want your media saved. It supports both the internal storage and SD cards.

        It comes with material design and dark theme by default, provides great user experience for easy usage. The lack of internet access gives you more privacy, security and stability than other apps.

        Contains no ads or unnecessary permissions. It is fully opensource, provides customizable colors.

        <b>Check out the full suite of Simple Tools here:</b>
        https://www.simplemobiletools.com

        <b>Facebook:</b>
        https://www.facebook.com/simplemobiletools

        <b>Reddit:</b>
        https://www.reddit.com/r/SimpleMobileTools
    </string>
    <!--
        Haven't found some strings? There's more at
        https://github.com/SimpleMobileTools/Simple-Commons/tree/master/commons/src/main/res
    -->
</resources>
